CHANYAPHAT METHA

24 YEARS OLD ANALYST



: 091-739-1050



: chanyaphat.mth@gmail.com



: SamutPrakan, Thailand

PROFILE INFO

I've been working as a logistics analyst for about a year now. Before that, I was a Java programmer intern. from two different forms of work, I gained a lot of experience and have studied and understood myself. And from experience Makes me interested in developing myself and improving as a Web Developer.

WORK EXPERIENCE

- **Analyst, Supply Chain Management** DKSH (Thailand) Limited Jul 2022 - Present
- Effectively prepare supply chain reports and analyses to facilitate management decision making
- Support for preparing supply chain strategic initiatives/programs to optimize supply chain performance
- Data Accuracy
- Java programmer (intern) Cube SoftTech.Co., Ltd. Jan 2022 - May 2022 (4 mos)
- Learning about the MVC Framework (JSP, Spring, Struts2, and Hibernate).
- Develop and improve the project of a web application system.

EDUCATION HISTORY

Computer Engineering MaeFahLuang University | 2018 - 2021

SKILL

















Python



Power Platform



